♪ All the leaves are brown ♪
(♪ All the leaves are brown ♪)
♪ And the sky is gray ♪
(♪ And the sky is gray ♪)
♪ I've been for a walk ♪
(♪ I've been for a walk ♪)
♪ On a winter's day ♪
(♪ On a winter's day ♪)
♪ I'd be safe and warm ♪
(♪ I'd be safe and warm ♪)
♪ If I was in L.A. ♪
(♪ If I was in L.A. ♪)
♪ California dreamin' ♪
(♪ California dreamin' ♪)
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
♪ Stopped into a church ♪
♪ I passed along the way ♪
♪ Well, I got down on my knees ♪
(♪ Got down on my knees ♪)
♪ And I pretend to pray ♪
(♪ I pretend to pray ♪)
♪ You know the preacher like the cold ♪
(♪ Preacher like the cold ♪)
♪ He knows I'm gonna stay ♪
(♪ Knows I'm gonna stay ♪)
♪ California dreamin' ♪
(♪ California dreamin' ♪)
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
♪ All the leaves are brown ♪
(♪ All the leaves are brown ♪)
♪ And the sky is gray ♪
(♪ And the sky is gray ♪)
♪ I've been for a walk ♪
(♪ I've been for a walk ♪)
♪ On a winter's day ♪
(♪ On a winter's day ♪)
♪ If I didn't tell her ♪
(♪ If I didn't tell her ♪)
♪ I could leave today ♪
(♪ I could leave today ♪)
♪ California dreamin' ♪
(♪ California dreamin' ♪)
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
♪ California dreamin' ♪